Prediction markets say one thing, opinion polls say another,
and the news says something entirely different.
AFOS Analytics is the first open-source platform
that cross-references all three — in real time, side by side.
Right now we're tracking Brazil's 2026 presidential election,
with 14 more countries on the global map.
Every 30 minutes, the platform pulls live odds
from the world's largest prediction market.
It cross-references 200+ electoral polls registered with TSE,
from over 17 institutes.
And aggregates hundreds of headlines,
auto-categorized by topic.
Everything is free. Everything is open-source.
No login, no tracking, no paywall.
Built by a solo founder in Brazil, because electoral transparency
shouldn't be the monopoly of polling institutes.
If you care about how political risk is priced,
measured, and narrated — take a look.
AFOS Analytics has no ideological or partisan affiliation.
It only observes what the data shows.
Link in the description. Star us on GitHub.